♪ In the
not-too-distant future ♪
♪ Next Sunday A.D. ♪
♪ There was a guy named Joel ♪
♪ Not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ He worked at
Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his bosses
didn't like him ♪
♪ So they shot him into space ♪
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Now, keep in mind
Joel can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ To make his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot roll call ♪
♪ Cambot ♪
♪ Pan left ♪
♪ Gypsy ♪
♪ Hi, girl ♪
♪ Tom Servo ♪
♪ Crow ♪
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Then repeat to yourself,
"It's just a show, ♪
♪ "I should really just relax" ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
- IBM, CBS, RCA, the
CIA, the FBI, the NBA,
A&P, NBC, ABC, R. Crumb,
and C.P.O. Sharkey.
You see, they're all the same.
And what do I think?
I think, if life gives you
lemons, you make lemonade.
Good night, and may God bless.
- Hey, that was great.
- Hey, I didn't know
you guys were there.
- Stop, thank you.
Well, it's a work in progress.
It's part of my one-man show
called "Robot on the Run."
- Hey, look, we're
on, everybody.
Hi!
Hey, welcome to the
Satellite of Love.
We're having our art
Chautauqua today.
- [Woman] Commercial
sign in 15 seconds.
- Anyway, Tom, you
wanna do yours?
- Let's do it.
(Tom clears throat)
I was born the son of a
poor Filipino merchant.
I remember I would
sit on the stoop
of my tenement brownstone
on the Lower East Side.
I was...
- [Woman] Tom, your
line is, "I was crying."
- Thank you.
- [Woman] Commercial sign
in five, four, three, two,
commercial sign now.
- I was crying.
(Tom crying)
(upbeat music)
- Tom?
Mayo, I'm going to
make a recommendation
that you be dropped
from the program.
- Don't you do it!
Don't you do it!
I've got nowhere else to go!
I've got nothin'.
- Hey, pretty good.
- Yeah, pretty good.
- Okay, anyway,
I think it's time
to do the invention
exchange here.
What I've got isn't
really a new invention,
but it's a new kind
of guitar chord.
What you do, it's for
the dynamic endings
of your rock show.
This is the Mel Bay
chart right there.
It's an A-minor augmented
with an Eddie Van Halen
bolt action on the bottom.
- Cool.
- So when you get to the big
jams at the end of the concert,
you can play it.
Now, it takes two hands
to play this chord,
so at that point you have
your dynamic front man,
I guess Crow will do
it, will strum it.
Okay, on the count of three.
One, two, three.
(guitar chord ringing)
(explosion bangs)
(all coughing)
What do you think, sirs?
- Oh, great, get
Foghat on the phone.
Well, our experiment
this week, Joel,
is going to be sweeping
the country by storm.
Isn't that right, Frank?
That's right.
You know all the fads with
the young people today.
You know the kids today,
with their loud music,
hula hoops, fax machines, but
the biggest fad these days,
karaoke, woo!
What we've done is we've
invented a karaoke machine
that exclusively plays
public domain songs.
That's right, that
means you can sing
into your karaoke machine,
have as much fun as you want,
and not pay one cent
in artist royalties.
- That's right, Frank.
Now, what happens when you go
into your favorite karaoke bar
and you want to hear "I
Want to Know What Love is"
by Foreigner?
- People vomit?
- No, Lou Gramm, songwriter,
and Chess King, spokesmodel,
gets a big fat royalty check,
and that means lots of money.
So, Joel, we've
loaded our machine
only with public domain songs.
All free of copyright, all
owned by you, the people.
- That's right.
You wanna hit the
roll there, Jerry?
- You get "The Battle
Hymn of the Republic."
- The immortal "Ba
Ba Black Sheep."
- turgid and bittersweet
"Gregorian Chant number 5."
- The impish "Twinkle
Twinkle Little Star."
- Mozart's "The Magic Flute,"
and there's so much more.
But your experiment this week,
Joel, is called "Pod People".
It has nothing to do with pods.
It has nothing to
do with people.
It has everything
to do with hurting.
And we're going to
sing you into it
with our new public
domain karaoke machine.
Hit it, Frank.
♪ Ave Maria ♪
(all shouting)
(alarm blaring)
- [Joel] Boy, it's a good thing
we got those new heads on.
- [Tom] Great experiment, Joel.
Great, great invention there.
- [Joel] Oh, pod people
got no reason to live.
- [Tom] Isn't that
Nia Peeples' brother?
Pod Peeple?
- [Joel] Mm-hmm.
- [Tom] No.
And she's married to
Maury Povich, right?
- [Joel] No, you're
thinking of Connie Chung.
That's Cheston.
- [Tom] Sorry.
- [Crow] Ooh.
- [Joel] William Anton.
I think that's Susan
Anton's half-brother.
- [Tom] Could be.
- [Crow] Which half?
- [Tom] Huh?
- [Joel] Better half?
Whoa, it's the Iron Maiden dude.
Check him out.
- [Crow] Hey!
I believe I'll use my putter.
Fore.
- [Joel] For what?
- [Crow] For hittin', guys.
- [Joel] Oh, this is
where the Swamp Thing
versus the sweet thang.
- [Tom] Ooh.
- [Crow] Ah.
- [Tom] Ah, the
tears of a clown.
- [Joel] Faruk Alatan?
I went to school
with Faruk Alatan.
(Tom chuckling)
- [Tom] Let's go skin
it and eat it now.
That's not a Spalding.
It's a Piquer Simon-Jack
Gray signature ball.
- [Crow] Huh.
I dare you to eat it.
- [Tom] No, you eat it.
Lick it first.
- [Joel] That one's
hard on pants.
Boy, that guy's got some
unfortunate skin, all right.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
- [Joel] Really
unfortunate skin.
- [Tom] Yeah.
- [Crow] Emergency 911.
- [Tom] A man falls.
Stunned by a monster.
- [Joel] My baby.
- [Tom] Oh, boldly backing away
from where no man
has gone before.
- [Crow] Car sick.
(all humming)
- [Tom] Look.
Between a rock
and a hard planet.
(Crow laughs)
- [Tom] Come on and dance.
- [Joel] I'm Curly
Neal, to show you how.
- [Crow] It was a
dark and stormy night.
I'd taken a creative
writing course.
- [Joel] Daktari.
- [Crow] Oh, I love
taking rides in the bog.
- [Man] You sure
this is the place?
- [Man] Sure I'm sure.
- [Tom] I'm sure that you're
sure that I'm sure I'm sure.
- [Crow] Sure?
- [Tom] Sure.
- [Man] Well, I think I'm sure.
- [Tom] Think you're
sure I'm sure.
- [Crow] Hey, does
he look dorky enough?
(Tom laughing)
- [Tom] Dorky Park.
- And you think you
know it all, don't ya?
- I just don't want
to spend a night out
in this crap for nothin'.
- For Christ's sake, will
you keep your voices down?
There's rangers around here.
- [Joel] Let's grab
the pic-a-nic baskets
and scram, Boo-Boo.
- [Tom] Meanwhile,
a few miles away.
- [Joel] Darren, did
you just hear a comet?
(thunder rumbling)
- [Crow] Huh.
Now, this guy's got
Renaissance Festival
written all over him.
- [Joel And Tom] Huzzah!
(thunder rumbling)
- [All] Lions and tigers,
and bears, oh, my!
Lions and tigers, and bears.
- [Joel] Oh, my!
- [Tom] Well, time
to start camping.
You dress up as
Oscar Wilde, and I'll
sing Noel Coward songs.
Camping! (chuckling)
- [Man] This way.
- [Crow] Yeah, whatever.
- [Tom] Tonight on Music
from Hearts of Space,
we'll go on a cosmic joyride
with some space music
by various bay area artists.
But first...
(thunder rumbling)
- [Man] There, that's the nest.
We'll make a fortune
with that lot.
They're nightingale's eggs.
- [Matt] I'll believe that
when they've hatched out.
- [Man] Lay off, will you, Matt?
- [Joel] Just lay off.
- [Matt] Here.
- [Joel] Perfect.
- Go to the truck and
bring a ladder, Sam.
- [Tom] I didn't get cast
in the Lorne Greene role
for nothin'.
(thunder rumbling)
- There's something very
strange going on in that light.
Look, over there.
- Didn't you hear me?
Go get that damn ladder.
- Okay.
- Move it!
- Heil Hitler.
- [Joel] I'm going, I'm going.
Jeepers.
- [Tom] First up
on Hearts of Space,
John Tesh with
"Whispering Firestorm."
Then it's Yanni with
"Snoremaster of Trafalgamar."
Then comes bay area
musician Del Mondo,
with his Sominex
suite in D-flat.
Then a synthesized
interplanetary
salute to Perry Como.
At the end of the hour,
we'll have information
about the types of sedatives
used by tonight's artists
on Music from the
Hearts of Space.
(cat meowing)
- [Joel] Football practice.
- [Tom] Puma?
Puma.
- [Crow] Spielberg?
(cat yowling)
- [Crow] Kitty.
Oh, Mittens, are
you eating gerbils?
- [Boy] Naughty kitty.
- [Joel] You must be punished.
Wow, his room's
becoming a disco.
- [Tom] Neat.
(cat meows)
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] It's the ABC
Movie of the Week.
(Tom laughs)
- [Tom] Hmm, what
pretentious crap.
- [Joel] Well, that
guy's gonna get
his presidential
physical fitness award.
It's a done deal.
(Crow grunts)
(Tom grunts)
- [Crow] Come on, you wuss.
- [Joel] Come on,
you gotta want it.
- [Crow] Hey, Dad hid
the eggs good this year.
- [Tom] Whoa.
- [Joel] That darn cat.
Huh?
- [Tom] Ooh!
- [Crow] Next time on MacGyver.
- [Joel] I do believe in spooks.
I do believe in spooks.
I do, I do, I do, I do,
I do, I do.
Good night.
- [Tom] Huzzah!
- [Man] Ha!
Did you see that?
- [Tom] Speak Middle English.
- Did you see it?
What?
What the hell are
you talking about?
Looked like like a huge ball
of fire crashed over there.
- Probably a bolt of lightning.
- It was no bolt of lightning.
I tell you something
crashed back there.
- What's going on?
I just saw something.
- Nothing.
- [Crow] Here, hold my purse.
- I swear to you, I saw
something crash back there.
I don't know, maybe a meteorite.
- Forget it, Sam.
Just go and get--
- [Tom] Push him over now.
- The ladder, will you?
Go on.
- [Tom] I love that one.
- And don't take all night.
- Wish we brought Bill along
instead of that crazy moron.
- Bill?
He's changed sides.
Works for the rangers now.
- [Joel] Bill jumped the fence?
- Bill on the side of the law?
That's incredible.
- [Tom] Swings both ways now.
- Let's try that
nest over there.
- [Joel] Hey, looks
like Yoda's home.
Luke?
Use the Force, Luke.
- [Crow] Hmm.
Nah.
(Crow snorting)
Ah, ah, it's clearing now.
- [Joel] With a name like
Smuckers raspberry preserves,
you know it's good.
This inflamed
tissue, the burning,
we'd better put some peroxide.
Smuckers brand peroxide.
- [Crow] I'll get a hanky.
- [Tom] Welcome to Laserium.
Tonight, music by Rick Wakeman.
(Tom humming)
- [Crow] A ladder.
That's a rope.
Idiot.
(Tom humming)
- [Tom] Oh, forget this.
I'm gettin' outta here!
- [Joel] I'm no longer
your whipping boy.
I ain't gonna work on
Maggie's farm no more.
(Joel laughing)
- [Joel] If you can't find
'em, grind 'em, right?
Grind a pound for me, man.
- [Tom] This Outward Bound
is really broadening him.
(man gasps)
- Well worth the trouble.
- Hey, let me have a look.
- [Joel] Good idea.
Hmm.
- [Tom] What have we here?
- [Joel] These are kola nuts.
These are un-kola nuts.
- These will pay the
rent for a while.
Where's Sam?
- [Crow] He's paying the rent.
- Hell, I don't know.
Should've been back
by now, though.
Hey, what if the son
of a has run out on us?
- And taken the truck, too.
- [Crow] Don't touch him there.
- Come on.
(upbeat music)
(eerie music)
- [Crow] Now Mr. Science is
gonna show us the white cells.
- [Tom] Put that down.
D'oh.
- [Crow] Oh, clean
up on aisle seven.
- [Joel] It's a
Gold'n Plump chicken!
- [Crow] Ugh.
- [Joel] Ugh.
- [Tom] Ooh, he
should've checked
the freshness date on those.
- [Crow] Over easy.
Oh, what is he, an L.A. cop?
- [Tom] Man exploring
his territory here.
- [Crow] Ouch.
- [Joel] I guess we know which
came first now, don't we?
(all groaning)
(creature growls)
- [Crow] Wanna make a movie,
you gotta break some eggs.
- [Tom] Bawk, bawk, bawk.
Cluck, cluck, cluck.
- [Joel] Oh my goodness,
it's the Easter Bunny,
and is he ever mad.
- [Crow] Hey, this guy
looks like Norm Abrams
getting killed.
- [Tom] Hmm.
- [Crow] Hear that?
- [Crow] Sounds like Norm Abrams
getting killed by
a giant chicken.
- [Tom] I gotta
walk off those eggs.
Whew, my cholesterol
count's way up.
- [Crow] Morning comes
to cheap white trash.
- Was this it?
- Yeah.
- [Crow] Yeah.
- [Matt] I knew it.
Son of a ran out on us.
- [Man] Ah, looks like we
spend the night out here.
- [Joel] You feel
comfortable sharing
a sleeping bag with me?
- [Tom] Ooh.
- [Matt] All the camping
equipment was in the pickup.
- [Man] So what?
Won't be the first
time you've dropped it.
Come on.
- [Tom] D'oh.
Hey, it's White Fang, and
he's stealing those bifocals.
- [Joel] They came to
Earth to steal bifocals.
- [Tom] Well, it's not his
prescription, I don't think.
- [Crow] I've gone blind.
I'm looking at the
back of my retinas.
- [Joel] No, it's
just the movie.
- [Crow] I'm blind.
- [Tom] The movie went blind.
- [Crow] Oh.
Wish I had gone blind.
- [Tomorrow] Luke, finish
your training, you will.
(thunder rumbling)
- [Joel] Bambi, humans
are basically good.
- [Tom] Check that.
- [Crow] You know,
Mom, you never hear
the one with your name on it.
- See that?
Game around here isn't
usually at all nervous.
- [Joel] My bloodlust
cannot be sated.
The light trembling
of a fawn as it lay
dying in my arms, you know.
- [Matt] Christ, you're
beginning to sound like Sam.
- [Tom] Son of Sam.
- Why or what, but I
got a funny feeling,
and I don't like it.
- [Joel] I've gotta kill
something is what I gotta do.
- [Crow] Gino Vannelli?
- [Joel] Yee.
- [Tom] Needs a shave.
- [Joel] Ugh.
- [Tom] Ooh.
Right in the eye.
- [All] Ooh.
- [Tom] Whoa!
Woo.
- [Joel] The helpless
cough of a squirrel
with a crushed face, that's
what life's all about.
- [Matt] What's the big hurry?
- [Man] The big hurry's I
wanna get the hell outta here.
- [Tom] I'm doing
a one-man show.
Leslie Nielsen, Leslie
Nielsen, Leslie Nielsen.
- I tell you, there's
something weird going on.
You stick around if
you like, I'm movin'.
- [Tom] Movin' on.
- [Crow] Hey, you may
wanna wax that bikini hair.
- [Tom] Oof!
Oh, you know, even
the movie "The Fog"
didn't have this much fog.
- [Joel] Uh-huh.
You know, the entry wound
of a shot is a kill.
- Okay.
- Please.
- [Matt] At least we'd
have four walls and a roof.
- [Man] And a jail
cell tomorrow.
- [Matt] Oh yeah,
guess you're right.
- [Tom] Eh, forget about that.
Hi, God.
Look, there's Julie
Andrews, and she's on fire!
- [Crow] Good.
- [Tom] Sorry, Jules.
- [Crow] You know, this scene
didn't originally appear
in the movie, but
they restored it.
Aren't you glad?
- [Tom] Oh, thank you, AMC.
Huh.
Mm-hmm.
- [Crow] Ah, it's the cameraman!
He's looking through
the wrong lens!
- [Joel] Oh, that comb used
to belong to Keith Richards.
- [Crow] Ugh, ew.
- Look what I got
here, Uncle Bill.
- Huh, centipede.
- It's a lithobius forficatus.
- To me, it's a centipede.
It's always been
called a centipede.
- [Crow] He's a loving
and giving caregiver.
- What have you got there?
- A lithobius forficatus.
- [Man] Centipede.
- Well, chuck the
filthy thing away.
- It's for my insect collection.
- Then, take it up
to your room, okay?
- Can I go out and find
some more specimens?
- Later, you've got to help
your uncle in the cellar.
Now then, finish your breakfast.
- [Tom] Aww.
- [Crow] Oops, wrong bowl.
(all groaning)
(lively music)
- [Tom] 3M today, a
more vibrant future
for the plastic
resin-based industries!
Ah, finally a movie
for our generation.
Swingin'.
Woo.
♪ Get your bike ready,
leather jacket on ♪
- [Joel] Hey, it's Greg Brady!
- [Tom And Crow] Cool.
♪ Let the engine go ♪
- No, hold it, hold it.
It stinks.
- [Crow] We agree.
- Let's take it
again from the top.
- [Crow] Here's your
coffee, I made it special.
I'll be right over here.
Bye.
- You guys are all
over the place.
- [Tom] Yeah, you're
up in the mountains,
you're in the studio,
you're in a cave,
you're in a shotgun
shack, you're in
another part of the world.
You're on top of
Old Smokey there.
Huh.
You're all over the place.
- [Crow] We're just as
confused as you are, folks.
- [Tom] Ah, the heck
with this, Norm.
Let's go down to the
suburbs and crash
through a school window.
- [Crow] Hey, okay.
Hey, you hear about Phil?
He got hit by a
truck last night.
- [Tom] Ooh, down
by the salt lick?
- [Crow] Yeah.
- [Tom] Oh, what a shame.
- [Man] Ah, here they come.
- [Joel] Walkin'
down the street.
They get the funniest looks
from everyone they meet.
- [Tom] Wait, those aren't deer.
- [Crow] Well, let's shoot 'em.
They're not wearing orange.
- [Joel] Well, they're gonna die
in that Samurai Jeep anyway.
- [Crow] You're still in first.
- [Crow] No, move,
you don't know
how to drive a stick, do you?
- [Man] Oh, hell,
don't say they're gonna
have problems, not now.
- [Crow] They're gonna
- [Man] Christ.
No.
There they go.
They're okay.
Good riddance.
- Now we can kill us some
game in peace and quiet.
- [Tom] Do you realize
what you just said?
(Matt laughs)
- [Matt] Or maybe just
go and rest in the cabin.
- [Joel] Huzzah.
- I say we take a rest.
(all shouting)
♪ Kick her into gear ♪
♪ Steady as she goes ♪
♪ Am I flying overdrive ♪
- [Tom] Flying over trout?
♪ Heading down the highway ♪
- [Tom] Hey, you think the
mike's picking up their dancing?
♪ All I wanna feel is
the wind in my eyes ♪
- [Crow] Lyrics by Mrs.
Johnson's Kindergarten Class.
- [Tom] Wind in my eyes?
♪ All systems ready to go ♪
- [Joel] All victims
ready to skull?
♪ Hear the engines roar now ♪
♪ Idiot control now ♪
♪ Idiot control ♪
- [Crow] Hey, Greg
Louganis is so talented.
- [Joel] Cute, too.
- [Tom] Young Republicans,
they're so hip!
- [Joel] This might be
Mike Curb Congregation's
best album ever!
♪ Burning rubber tires ♪
- [Tom] Woo!
- That's nice.
- Now they got it together.
- [Tom] Oh, yeah, they
got it together now.
(Tom laughing)
- [Crow] Hmm, hmm, hmm,
ceiling needs painting.
- He is really good.
- Good?
He's the best.
- [Tom] Oh, I could say...
- [Joel] Just
leave it like that.
♪ Hear the engines roar now ♪
♪ Hear the young potato ♪
♪ Idiot control now ♪
♪ Hear the engines roar now ♪
♪ Hideous control now ♪
♪ Digging Minnie Pearl now ♪
♪ Hear the engines roar now ♪
♪ Wheels on fire,
burning rubber tires ♪
- [Tom] Woo!
♪ Hear the engines roar now ♪
Nice song, but I think it
needs a hook or something.
♪ Hear the engines roar now ♪
Get down, Crow.
- [Crow] I can't.
Back up.
♪ Hear the engines roar now ♪
- [Tom] Woo!
- [Joel] If these guys
get any more soul,
we'll have to order
out for greens.
- Okay.
- Hmm?
- Huh?
(women sighing)
(men sighing)
- Well?
- [Tom] Hmm?
- It stinks.
- [Tom] D'oh.
- [All] Wah, wah, wah.
- Well, what's the
matter with it?
- Who knows, it was great.
- I hope you're joking.
- I never joke about my living.
- Well, I thought it
was great this time.
- Great, yeah.
Kathy was half-asleep,
and you, Tracy,
you were blasting
out like a foghorn.
- What's wrong with him, then?
Did he get up on the wrong
side of the bed, huh?
- [Crow] You should know.
- [Tom] Hey, shh.
- And you.
- Me, what?
Come on, out with it.
- You came in half a beat late!
- [Joel] Ooh.
- [Sharon] What are you
talking about, Rick?
- Back in a minute.
- [Sharon] I came
in half a beat late?
- I'm not going
to argue, Sharon.
You came in late.
- Come on, Rick,
give me a break.
You're always early.
You're impossible to follow.
- [Man] Yay!
Fantastic, everybody.
- [Joel] Hey, it's
Andy Travis from WKRP!
- Gary's really excited
about this take.
Why don't you ask him?
- [Tom] Hmm?
- Hmm?
- Hey guys, the fun's over.
- Well, I still say you
were all fantastic, really.
- It's gonna be a hit for sure.
You wanna hear it again?
- [All] No, no, no.
- That's okay, Gary.
It's been a long day.
We'll hear it on Monday.
Thanks.
Have a nice weekend.
- [Crow] But it's Wednesday.
- [Tom] Long weekend.
- And now, let's
get out of here.
Let's get up into
those mountains
and breathe a little fresh air.
- After the atmosphere in
here, it'll probably kill us.
- Tracy, go pick up the scores.
- [Joel] And my
leather clown suit.
- Me and my big mouth.
- Place is really great.
You'll love it up there.
- Hey, Gary, how about it, huh?
- Sorry honey, got
a mess of work.
- Oh, come on, Gary.
You'll have a wonderful time.
I'll belong to
you, soul and body.
- [Crow] No, I just ate, thanks.
- I'm sorry, Tracy, it's
been a long week, and, well--
- Okay, don't worry.
I get the message.
I know I'm not your type.
What the hell?
There's always Robert Redford.
- [Tom] Oh, we gotta go, guys.
- Come on, give me a break.
- [Tracy] That's
what I was doing.
- [Crow] Oh.
- Don't call us, we'll call you.
- [Joel] She should be
more accessible, you know?
- So long, super stud.
- All right, all right,
let's do it again.
You come in late, girls,
again, you're out.
All right?
All right, from the top.
(lively music)
♪ With a pickle mind, we
kick the nipple beers ♪
♪ Steady as a goat,
we're flying over trout ♪
♪ Ghetto down the highway,
at the speed of light ♪
♪ All I wanna feel now
is the wind in my eyes ♪
♪ Sack of monkeys in my pocket ♪
♪ My sister's ready to go ♪
♪ Hear the engines roar now ♪
♪ Idiot control now ♪
♪ Hideous control now ♪
♪ Ninny on the road now ♪
♪ Minnie in control ♪
♪ Wheels on fire ♪
♪ Burning rubber tires ♪
- Woo!
- He's pretty good.
- Good?
He's the best.
♪ Blurry jelly rolls now ♪
♪ Hiddy lets it go now ♪
♪ Needy inches bow down ♪
♪ Pitying a poor boy ♪
♪ Hear the engines roar ♪
♪ Bees on pie ♪
♪ Burning rubber tires ♪
(Gypsy sighing)
- Oh, great.
Pretty good.
What do you think?
- It stinks.
(upbeat music)
- Mom.
♪ Hear the engines roar now ♪
- [Tom] Woo.
That was a hot session, huh?
Oh, yeah.
- Look, Sharon,
honey, I'm sorry.
I got all uptight.
- [Tom] D'oh.
- This is important to me,
this LP, you know that.
Don't you?
Just forget it, will you?
You know I didn't mean anything.
- [Tom] Ah, kiss
me, you big lug.
- [Tom] Mm-mm.
- Hey, you've got all weekend.
- [Joel] Oh, that's right.
All for fun.
- [Tom] Oh, that's sweet, huh?
- [Joel] Oh, neat, let's go.
- [Crow] And they have Pringles.
- You think the
weather's going to hold?
- [Tom] No, I think
it's just going to stop.
- Hey, where did you
say we were going?
- [Crow] To hell.
- Cinder National Forest.
It's a fantastic place.
So peaceful and so quiet.
- Not a soul for
miles, I suppose.
- [Joel] I'm not bringing mine.
- It's really out of the way.
Just a few rangers
and a lot of bears.
- I guess I'll just
have to find a ranger
or a bear to sleep with, then.
- [Tom] What are you saying?
Oh.
Oh, sorry, wrong movie.
- I'm cold.
I didn't bring my jacket.
- [Crow] Or your brain.
- Do you mind if I put on
one of yours, Rick, darling?
- [Crow] Look,
Pocahontas, Rick's mine.
- Somebody else
needs warming up.
- Who the hell is that?
- Hi, y'all.
I'm Laura Stapleton.
- [Joel] Maureen Stapleton?
- [Crow] Naw.
- [Tom] Looking good.
- Oh, Ricky, you were wonderful.
Marvelous.
You were all great.
We're gonna have such
fun this weekend.
- [Tom] Uh-oh.
- Yeah, great fun.
- [Tom] Ooh.
- Sharon!
- What's got into that--
- [Crow] Girl.
- Are you all right, Rick?
- [Crow] All right in the bags?
S'all right.
- [Laura] Open this door!
- Who on Earth made
you invite her along?
- [Laura] What's going on?
- Forgot we met the other day.
I guess I must've told her
about the weekend by accident.
- Yeah, accidentally on purpose.
- Never thought
she'd actually come.
- Well, tell her to get lost.
- I can't do that, can I?
Turns out she's the daughter
of one of the bosses here.
Makes her part of the
establishment, doesn't it?
And she happens to
like the way I perform.
Anyway, an artist has to think
about his public, doesn't he?
- [Tom] Can't argue with that.
- Especially if your
public has boobs like that.
- [Tom] Joel, what are boobs?
- [Joel] You know,
like Jethro Bodine?
- [Tom] Oh, boobs.
Okay.
- Sharon, I think
you're making a mountain
out of a molehill.
(Tom clears throat)
- Leave me alone,
I'm going home.
- [Crow] To change, I hope.
- Believe me, it's
not what you think.
- [Joel] It's what
you're wearing.
- Of course not.
It's probably worse.
Anyway, that's it.
I'm finished with him.
- Listen, Sharon.
Deep down, that guy
is nuts about you.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
- Making out with chicks is
part of his act as an artist.
- [Joel] Hmm.
- One today, a
different one tomorrow.
- [Joel] See, cheating is hip.
- Accept the fact.
And if you love him, stand
up and fight for him.
- [Tom] Enjoy being used.
- There's no way you lose out.
Especially against
some idiot like that.
So cool it.
And relax.
- Okay.
- Brian's right,
you know, Sharon.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
- Yes, isn't he always?
- Why couldn't I fall
in love with him?
(all laughing)
- [Joel] And then they, oh.
- [Tom] Come on, knuckleheads.
- [Crow] Still friends.
Yeah.
Hey, try to be nice to your
boyfriend's girlfriend,
boyfriend.
- [Tom] There, that'll keep 'em.
- [Tom] Uncle Bill?
- [Crow] Jody?
- [Joel] Buffy?
- [Tom] Mr. French?
- [Joel] Mrs. Beasley?
- [Tom] Chief?
- [Crow] McCloud?
(Tom laughing)
(tense music)
- [Crow] Boy, I hate Kenny.
- [Joel] Oh, that's not Kenny.
We like this kid.
- [Crow] Oh.
Hey, it's Desi and Lucy
in "The Big, Big Trailer!"
(Tom chuckling))
- [Joel] It's neat, huh?
- [Crow] Yeah.
- [Tom] Is this white Reggae?
♪ What should I do? ♪
♪ It's getting late ♪
♪ I'm feeling blue ♪
- [Joel] Oh, this is Morrissey.
- [Crow] Oh!
- [Joel] I love it.
♪ I sometimes think ♪
♪ It's one of the jokes ♪
- [Tom] Ooga.
- [Joel] It's a kooky
radio, isn't it?
- [Crow] Yeah, it
goes in my ear.
(Tom laughing)
- [Tom] Boy, you know,
Ringo did some bad songs,
but this is really embarrassing.
- [Joel] Yeah.
♪ What should I do ♪
- [Crow] Retire.
♪ She hasn't come ♪
♪ I'm feeling blue ♪
- [Joel] Hmm, this
should fit over my head.
♪ That you will
come at the end ♪
- [Tom] What?
♪ Why you didn't
call and tell me ♪
- [Crow] Give me that.
I'll scratch your eyes out.
- Found a worse road than this?
(Joel laughs)
- [Joel] Fun.
Levity.
- [Tom] Ah, the von Trapp
Family Singers on the road.
- [Crow] Hope they
find some Nazis.
(Tom laughing)
- [Tom] Enjoy the good
life in retirement.
Scenic back roads, Morrissey
songs 24 hours a day.
- [Joel] And it really came
together when Mom sang along.
♪ You call me to
tell me you love me ♪
♪ You play the same game again ♪
♪ What do you want from me ♪
- [Tom] Oh, oh,
Joel, Joel, Joel,
I'm tripping,
tripping, tripping.
- [Crow] Talk him down,
Joel, talk him down.
- [Joel] It's the
Echoplex, buddy.
- [Tom] Whew.
I was worried.
- [Crow] Hey, look,
we paid for the van,
we're gonna film it.
- [Tom] Paid for the song, too.
Gonna use it all.
- [Joel] Oh, terrific, we're
saved by the Gates of Hell.
- [Crow] Hey, what is it
about the Gates of Hell
that compels people
to wander into 'em?
- [Joel] It's because of
Smuckers raspberry preserves.
- [Crow] Man, what's
he going to do,
borrow a cup of
sugar from Satan?
- [Joel] No, he's
gonna borrow a cup
of Smuckers raspberry jam.
It's most like real fruit.
- [Tom] Beastmaster?
- [Crow] Ringo?
- [Joel] Axel?
- [Tom And Crow] Sinead?
- [Tom] Chief?
- [Crow] McCloud?
Wow, specimen jackpot.
- [Tom] Just put
away his Dinty Moore.
- [Crow] Oh, that'll
go great in his
alien mutant hell beast
from space collection.
(boy gasps)
- [Tom] It says, "Don't
laugh, it's paid for."
- [Joel] In Braille?
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
- Hey, one of you go and
help Rick collect firewood.
- [Joel] I'll go, I wanna die.
(electronic chirping)
- [Tom] Syntho birds.
- [Joel] Hmm.
- [Crow] Hey, it's
a Casio forest.
- [Joel] They parked
next to a data stream.
- [Crow] Hmm.
- [Tom] Hmm.
- Rick?
Ricky, wait for me.
Hey.
- [Crow] Hey, put the
Casio back in the van.
- I don't think the
others like me being here.
- [Joel] Duh.
- They haven't
said a word to me.
- Ignore them, then.
- Oh, sure.
- [Tom] I would, but they
dry-click their revolvers at me.
- What brought you here?
Me or them?
- You, and you're right.
I don't care.
Kiss me, Ricky.
- [Crow] Where?
- Not now, later.
They're waiting for us.
- I only asked you to kiss me.
Don't you want to?
- [Crow] No, I... (murmuring)
You got my gum. (murmuring)
- Rick!
Where are you, Rick?
- [Crow] Over here.
- Hold on!
I'm coming!
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
- [Crow] This is CNN.
- [Woman] Tommy.
- [Joel] Have you been playing
with the gatekeeper
again, Tommy?
- [Brian] Well...
- [Tom] Mmm.
- If nothing else--
- [Tom] Oh, you know,
Steve tastes great.
- I wish everybody liked them.
- [Tom] A little more pelvis?
- What do you
think, Laura, dear?
- Mmm.
Real good.
- Hmm, you look like
you're enjoying it.
- My mother's just the best
darn cook in the world.
She taught me to
enjoy good eating.
- [Tom] Mmm.
- Especially steaks, huh?
- Not only.
All kinds of meat.
- [Tom] Pelvis.
- Sounds like a talented
lady, your mother.
- [Tom] My mother was a saint!
- You guys laughing
at me all the time.
- [Joel] We're laughing
with you, dear heart.
- Oh, yeah, sure.
I know that you hate me.
You're jealous, aren't ya?
Because Ricky likes me.
Well, that's the way the
cookie crumbles, honey.
- [Tom] Ooh.
- Tell her what we did
in the woods, Ricky.
She'd love to know.
Right, Sharon?
(Laura gasps)
- [Tom] Coffee?
(Laura huffs)
- Laura!
- [Tom] You forgot
your breakfast!
- [Tracy] I think I
better go after her.
- No, leave her
alone for a while.
Let her cool off.
- [Crow] Or get
eaten by creatures.
- [Tom] Snap an ankle,
die of exposure.
- You know, we have
been very hard on her.
- [Crow] Yeah, but it's a good
chance to thin out the cast.
(Tom imitating weeping)
- [Tom] I don't
even like coffee.
(Tom slurping)
- [Joel] Only half a cup?
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
- [Tom] Don't you
like the rich taste?
- [Tom] Mmm.
- [Crow] Dad?
- [Tom] Mummy?
- Ricky?
- [Crow] Mr. Drysdale?
- [Joel] Mr. Eddie's father?
- [Laura] Don't play
games with me, please.
- [Crow] Mr. Douglas.
- [Tom] Mr. Haney.
- [Crow] Lisa?
- [Tom] Chief?
- [Crow] McCloud?
(upbeat music)
(mysterious music)
- Please come out.
- [Tom] Shaking the trees.
- Ricky, I'm frightened.
(Laura gasps)
- Hey, look at the
little birdie I caught.
- [Tom] It's a girl, you idiot.
- You know what, Matt?
You're a real blockhead.
You're just looking
to land up in jail.
- [Joel] Come on, I
can use her in my act.
Huzzah.
- I ain't doing nothing.
You better run.
- It's all forest that way.
She won't get far.
- [Tom] D'oh.
- [Matt] Come on.
- [Crow] And there,
on the handle, was,
you're not listening.
- Great weather for a picnic.
I read it in my horoscope.
- [Joel] My horoscope
said you'd be stalked
by a leather mug maker from
a Renaissance Festival.
(Laura panting)
- Jesus, that little
can run a lot faster
than I thought.
- Yeah, well, you're a jerk.
- [Tom] Ooh, touche.
Very clever.
(Laura gasps)
(creature growling)
(Laura screaming)
- [Tom] Next week on Mannix.
- God, what was that?
- [Crow] Sounded like
Laura leaping to her death.
- Laura?
- [Tom] Jerk.
Jerk.
Over there, jerk.
Come on, jerk.
Such a jerk.
- Come on.
- [Joel] Wait, did
we leave the iron on?
- Laura!
Where are you, Laura?
- [Joel] Tell Laura I love her.
- [Brian] Laura!
- [Tom] Huh?
Is your name Laura?
- [Man] Nothing
but trouble, Matt.
Let's get outta here fast.
- [Joel] Bitty-bitty-bitty.
Wanna dance, Buck?
- [Tom] Oh, it's Laura Palmer.
(thunder rumbling)
Soupy Sales.
- This way.
- [Crow] What, do you smell her?
- [Tom] Yeah, like a bloodhound.
- [Crow] Yeah.
- [Rick] There she is.
- [Tom] Don't move.
We'll come down.
- [Brian] Laura!
Laura!
She isn't dead, is she?
- I don't think so.
But she's sure in bad shape.
Get her legs.
- [Crow] Yeah, quick, move
her spine around a lot.
(imitating bones cracking)
- [Crow] Dope.
- [Tracy] Laura!
Rick!
- [Tom] Bosley?
- [Joel] Angels?
- [Tom] Chief?
- [Crow] McCloud?
- Daddy, where are you?
- [Tom] Daddy?
- [Joel] Leviathan?
- [Tom] Laverne?
- Where are they?
- There they are over there.
Oh, my god, what happened?
I don't know.
- [Tom] She's claiming
she's Anais Nin.
- Things could get
kinda tricky now.
This place is gonna be
swarming with rangers soon.
We better be on
our way outta here.
- [Joel] We shouldn't have
stole that pic-a-nic basket.
- We'll make for the old
hideout in the canyon, Big Bend.
- [Joel] Huzzah.
- Christ, that's miles away.
(thunder rumbling)
- Come on.
- [Tom] Quick, let's fold her.
- [Crow] Well, I'm so glad they
turned her into a vegetable.
- Give me one of the blankets.
- [Tom] No, that's okay.
I'm not cold.
- [Crow] It's for her.
- [Tom] Oh.
TRACY: Here,
this'll warm her up.
- [Tom] No thanks,
I'm not thirsty.
- [Crow] It's for her, for her.
- [Joel] For her.
- [Tom] She obviously
doesn't need it.
- [Brian] She's out cold.
- [Crow] Yeah.
- We've got to get
her to a hospital.
- [Joel] Or a bar.
- Hold on, Rick, it's
more than 50 miles.
In this weather, on these roads,
you wouldn't get very far.
- We have to do
something, Brian.
We can't just leave her.
- It's my fault.
I forced her to run away.
- Oh, Sharon, it
wasn't you, it was me.
She'll be all right, you'll see.
- [Joel] It's her fault.
- What can we do, Brian?
- [Crow] Jam a sandwich
down her throat.
- The refuge at Black Butte,
where there's a telephone,
and they can help us.
- Then, let's get out things.
Come on.
- [Tom] Meanwhile,
in another movie.
Ah, patience, gentle viewer.
This'll all make sense
in the end. (cuckles)
Not.
- [Crow] I wonder when Flo
and Alice are gonna get here.
- [Tom] Mel, at home.
Let me out!
I said let me out!
Ow, ow.
- [Crow] Shave and a haircut?
- [Tom] Two bits.
- [Woman] Tommy.
- [Crow] Just tending
the incubus, mother.
- Why haven't you
gone to bed yet?
- I did, Mom, but
kitty was meowing
and I thought maybe
he was hungry.
- Oh, he's already eaten
at least three times today.
- Then he certainly
shouldn't have any more.
- Okay, come on, into bed.
One of these days we're going
to have trouble with you two.
In you get.
- [Tom] And remember,
no wire hangers!
- Settle down.
Now, go to sleep, all right?
- Yes, Mom.
- [Tom] Good night, mother.
- [Joel] Good night, John-boy.
- [Tom] Good night, Hardcastle.
- [Joel] Good night, McCormick.
- [Tom] Good night, Chief.
- [Crow] Good night, McCloud.
(Tom chuckling)
- You all just wait and see.
You're gonna have
a new friend soon.
(Crow chuckles)
- [Crow] That's really
great, little kid.
- [Tom] Sad.
- [Joel] Spends a
lot of time alone.
Ugh.
Oh, he's trying
to hatch the egg.
What is he, Horton?
(Tom chuckling)
(Tom snores)
- [Tom] Okay, so
is this Movie A?
- [Joel] Beats me.
- [Tom] Well, let's see.
The hunters are in Movie A.
The kid was in Movie B.
- [Crow] Ah, this is
the Cowsills part.
This is Movie C, C.
- [Joel] I shouldn't
have had so much coffee.
I'll be right back.
- [Tom] Ooh, enter
the fog machine.
(mysterious music)
- [Joel] Come on, honey.
You're gonna love it here.
- Hello?
Anybody home?
- What do you want at
this time of night?
- We need help.
- Well, go and find
it somewhere else.
- Wait a minute, please!
Please, we need help!
- What's going on, Bill?
- Just a troublemaker.
- [Crow] Nah, Jehovah Witnesses.
- [Rick] Please, we need help.
- Open the door, Bill.
Go on.
- [Joel] Open the door.
- Please, ma'am, can
we use your phone?
There's been an accident.
- [Joel] She soiled herself.
- What kind of trouble?
- [Tom] Oh, please.
- She fell.
- Bring her in.
- [Tom] Accident.
- Follow me.
- This phone isn't working.
- [Crow] Give me that.
I'll show you how
to use a prop phone.
- All right?
- Yeah, fine.
- [Crow] Yeah, just a few more
rooms, and you'll be there.
Keep going.
- [Tom] Ooh, nice.
- The line's dead.
- There's been a rock fall.
The road's blocked.
The phone lines are
probably down, too.
- [Joel] There's no
way out of this film.
- God only knows how
you got this far.
- Did you get through
to the hospital?
- [Crow] No, it's a prop phone.
- No way.
The phone's screwed up.
- That's all we need.
- [Joel] Oh man, if it's
not one thing, it's another.
- [Brian] Surely must be
some way of getting help.
- [Tom] Hey, life stinks, man.
Deal with it.
- Not now there ain't.
- You sure?
- Of course I am.
- Come on, I'll make
you some coffee.
Don't worry.
She'll be all right.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
- [Woman] With a good
night's rest, she'll be
as right as rain in the morning.
- [Joel] Yeah, that's what
cures a crushed spine.
- [Tom] Uh-huh.
- What's going on?
- Nothing.
The phone's not working.
The road back to
town is blocked.
Looks like there's
no way out of here.
- But Laura needs help.
There must be some way.
- Doesn't look like it.
Not in this bloody wilderness.
You and your out
of the way places.
- [Tom] D'oh.
- [Sharon] Come on now, Rick--
- [Joel] Wow, a rock
group staying at my house?
Too much.
- [Rick] I know,
I'm not blaming you.
- It'll all be all right.
I know where we can get help.
- Please, Mrs...
- Stevens.
- Thank you.
- Molly Stevens.
- Tell us, Mrs. Stevens.
- [Joel] Molly Stevens.
- Just a few miles
from here there's
a forest ranger's cabin.
They've got a radio.
- Then what are we waiting for?
- Not now.
You'll have to
wait for daylight.
At night you wouldn't make it.
Anyway, since it's springtime,
the rangers will be out
searching for poachers.
I'm right, Bill, aren't I?
- [Crow] Oh, yeah,
I'll give you that one.
- Bill knows where
the patrols get to.
He'll take you there tomorrow.
Now you must get some rest.
It's no good worrying.
We've got plenty of space here.
So as soon as you
finish your coffee,
I'll show you to your room.
- [Brian] You're
being very kind.
- [Tom] Egg?
Say, egg.
There's a lot of people here.
(boy gasps)
Huh?
Ooh, we gotta go.
(all groaning)
- [Joel] Creamy living
chocolate center.
- [Tom] Ugh!
(upbeat music)
- Oh, hiya, Crow.
- Oh, hi.
- Whatcha doin'?
- Oh, we were just inspired
by the cool new-age music
of this movie, so we decided
to use the wall of keyboards
and make out own great
new new-age music.
You wanna help?
- Sure.
What can I do?
- Well, I could teach you
how to play the keyboards.
- Will it take long?
- No, of course not.
Come on over here.
Here, check this out.
Okay, put your hand, come
on, put your hand over here.
- [Crow] Okay.
- Put your finger down, see?
- Like that?
- Yeah.
- Ah.
- Yeah, you got
it, you're playing
a new-age chord now, okay?
- Hey.
- Just like Yanni.
All right, now, put
another finger down.
- Okay.
- See?
Now you're playing a Yanni lick.
Now, hold it down for an hour.
- Yeah.
- Now hold it down till
you get a record contract
from Windham Hill.
- Oh, hey, cool.
- See?
- Servo, check it out.
It's my new new-age Yanni lick.
Joel, hold on my new
new-age Yanni lick.
I gotta put my sandwich down.
- Okay, got it.
- This music's kind
of dull, isn't it?
- Yeah, but it's a good
way to make a lot of money
without a big
initial investment.
(Tom clearing throat)
- Okay.
And now, "Music From
Some Guys in Space."
Tonight on "Music From
Some Guys in Space,"
more fine new new-age
music and sounds
from super progressive bay
area new-age keyboardist
Joel Robinson.
Joel will be accompanied
on the wall of keyboards
by veteran minimalist
Crow T. Robot.
We invite you to sit back
and enjoy more repetitive
new-age music as we
cruise the space ways.
Come along, fellow
travelers, and enjoy music
from some guys in space.
(alarm blaring)
- Hey, we got movie
sign, you guys.
- It's movie sign, next
time on Emergency 911.
- Tom, you're stuck
in Shatner mode.
Come on, man, snap out of it.
Crow, wake up!
- Movie sign!
- What?
(all shouting)
- When I get a hold of that
Sam, I swear I'll kill him.
Standing us up here like this.
- Oh, it's not so bad.
There's a connection
I know who'll give us
at least, I'd say--
- [Tom] You awake, Crow?
- 3000 bucks for this lot.
- Yeah.
(Crow sighs)
- And how are we supposed
to get back to town, huh?
On foot?
- [Tom] Wait a minute, I'm, yep.
- It wouldn't be the first time.
(Tom chuckles)
- Why don't we take
the kids' camper?
- Are you crazy?
- [Joel] Can I think about it?
- Haven't you screwed
things up enough already?
Huh?
- [Crow] Well, he
did write the script.
- [Joel] Huzzah.
- What was that noise?
- Maybe it's the rangers.
- [Joel] Hey, Boo-Boo.
- [Tom] Eww.
Mm-hmm.
- What on Earth is that?
Looks like a cross
between a pig and a bear.
- [Crow] A pear?
- My god it's ugly.
- [Joel] Hey, you're no prize
yourself, Dan Folgelberg.
- Be careful.
It could be dangerous.
(gun clicks)
- Ah, it may be ugly, but
it appears harmless enough.
- [Joel] Hey, it's
Mr. Snuffleupagus.
- [Tom] Cute.
- Sure is a strange bird.
Think it could be
worth something?
- Yeah, maybe.
- [Tom] Maybe.
- Keep him busy.
- [Tom] Keep him busy?
- Hey, enjoying yourself?
Take a little night stroll?
Trouble is, the weather's a
little bit rough for that.
Isn't it?
- [Crow] Stop the
inane conversation.
- Go on talking.
- [Joel] You live
around here much?
- You must be hungry, huh?
Have some.
- [Crow] It's one
of you, only gamier.
- [Tom] Ew.
- [Matt] It won't hurt ya.
- [Joel] So, you
like Chinese food?
- [Matt] Help yourself.
- [Joel] Huh?
- [Tom] Mongolian barbecue?
- [Joel] Ha.
- [Tom] Oh.
- Matt, come on!
Give me a hand!
- [Crow] Get the drawn butter.
- Christ, he's strong.
I can't hold him.
- [Tom] Alf, no!
No, Alf!
(creature grunts)
- [Tom] Ooh.
Big mistake.
- [Crow] Hey, that
long nose must be handy
in hard-to-reach areas.
(Tom chuckling)
(Tom humming)
- [Tom] Just pad out the
scene here a little bit.
(all humming)
- [Joel] Hey, what gives?
I'm on the milk carton.
- You're hungry
again, aren't you?
There's no need
to worry, Trumpy.
You like that name,
don't you, Trumpy?
- [Crow] I prefer Milky Bear.
- I won't let anyone hurt you.
- [Joel] I named you
after Donald Trump.
- Hello.
Hey, look.
Look what I got for you.
- [Tom] Mucus.
- Oh, boy.
You sure are greedy, aren't you?
Wow, if you keep
drinking milk like that,
you're gonna grow
really big and strong.
Then we can play together.
You know what
playing is, Trumpy?
- [Crow] Yes, it's where
I break you in half.
- No?
I'll teach you.
We're gonna have such fun.
- [Tom] Foreigner.
Meanwhile in Movie C.
- [Crow] I think
this is Movie D.
- [Tom] Oh.
- [Crow] D for dumb.
(Tom chuckling)
- [Tom] Okay.
(boy gasps)
- [Joel] Oh, great.
- Oh, boy, how you've grown.
- [Joel] Yeah, during the
cutaway anything's possible.
- Keep growing like that, and
you won't fit any clothes.
Then what are we gonna do?
- Tommy, come on down
and eat your breakfast.
- You've gotta hide.
You understand?
You've gotta hide.
- Tommy, did you hear me?
- [Tom] Can you
feel me near you?
Oh, what a nightmare.
Ooh, I dreamt I was
a crappy actress
in a horrible monster film.
Hey, wait a minute.
- [Joel] Oh, no, she really
does have combination skin.
- [Crow] Ew.
- [Joel] Oh.
Oh, my goodness.
- [Crow] Oh, bad.
Big bad.
Big bad thing.
Help, everyone.
Big bad.
- [Sharon] Rick!
- [Joel] Hurry.
Big sale on flannel.
Everyone, come on.
- [Tom] Flannel?
Did she say, "flannel"?
- [Joel] Here, drink
this coffee, kid.
- [Crow] Oh, he's stealing
all the Nerf toast.
(Tracy gasps)
- [Tom] Hello, remember
us, the audience?
Could we see, please?
- [Joel] I think her
perm didn't take.
- [Crow] Ew.
(Tracy crying)
- [Crow] Well, come on, your
breakfast is getting cold,
and she's not
getting any warmer.
That means more
oatmeal for everyone.
- [Tom] Right.
- What happened, Mommy?
- It's nothing to
do with you, dear.
- [Tom] Go play with your
tripping hell beast, darling.
- But I don't want you
coming in here, understand?
Have you finished
your breakfast?
- Mm-hmm.
- Then you know what
you have to do now.
Run along.
(cat meowing)
- [Crow] Mmm.
Delicious kitty.
Oh.
Ouch.
Ooh, kitty's like a potato.
(birds chirping)
Oh, so nice.
Oh, where do I start?
It all looks so good.
Little winged potatoes.
Ouch, that's my snout.
Ow, let go.
Hmm.
This potato's got big ears.
Yes.
- [Tom] Mm-hm.
- [Crow] It's a whole buffet.
New potatoes, hmm.
- [Tom] Whoa!
- [Crow] Ah!
- [Tom] Oh, it's a rogue robot.
He's got the mange.
He's gone rogue.
We're gonna have to kill him.
Speak to me, boy.
(robot rattling)
Uh-oh.
- [Crow] Ah, never seen
one do that before.
Whoa!
- [Tom] Ooh, never seen
one do that before.
- [Joel] Oh, that's no good.
Uh-uh.
(Tom humming)
- [Crow] He's gonna
have to house train 'em.
He can't just keep
hauling that stuff out.
- I told you to
stay out of sight.
Nobody must see you.
- [Tom] He doesn't speak
your language, dickweed.
- If you wanna stay with
me, you've got to do
what I tell you.
- [Crow] I don't think so.
- You don't want them
to separate us, do you?
- [Joel] Carbon scoring
all over my droid.
- I've brought you
something special to eat.
Are you hungry now, Trumpy?
- [Crow] Yes.
- [Tom] Ooh, won't peanuts
get caught in his snout?
- [Crow] Oh, little potatoes.
- [Tom] Ooh.
- [Joel] Yeah.
- [Crow] Now you try.
- Do you want some more?
- [Joel] Oh, wait, let
me get the attachments.
You can do the couch.
- You know, sooner or
later, Mommy's gonna notice
all this food disappearing.
- [Tom] Then you'll
have to kill her.
- These we'll put
away for later.
- [Crow] No, more.
- Now we can play.
- [Crow] Like hell.
More food.
- You know how to play, Trumpy?
What do you know?
- [Crow] Food,
eating, the theater.
- Nothing?
- [Joel] Boy, I sure hope
Trumpy doesn't sneeze
and pistol-whip that
kid with peanuts.
- [Crow] Wow, never
thought about that.
- I'll show you how
to do a jigsaw, okay?
- [Tom] Oh, that's exciting.
- Here, come on.
- [Tom] Pente, the
ancient game of stones.
Hmm?
- You see?
The pieces go together.
- [Joel] Oh, if only
this film were so lucky.
- You understand?
It's easy.
- [Joel] Why are you looking
at me like that, Trumpy?
- Well, Trumpy, you get it?
- [Crow] No.
- No, hmm?
Well, let's try another game.
Gee, you must teach me one day.
All right.
Now, then, look at me.
- [Crow] Can I eat it?
It looks so good.
- Pay attention and
repeat what I do.
- [Tom] Like a potato?
(game beeping)
No, wait, wait.
Let me try again.
- Are you watching?
- [Tom] Damn.
No, no, that's not, there, okay.
Yeah, that's it.
Oh, he stinks.
- [Joel] Not very good, is he?
- [Crow] Uh-uh.
- [Tom] Yeah, that's great.
Give me that.
Huh?
- [Crow] Huh?
- [Tom] Oh, it's kooky.
- [Crow] Hey.
- Gee.
- [Joel] Trumpy, you
can do stupid things.
Isn't this Gary Numan
and the Tubeway Army?
- [Tom] Yep.
♪ In cars. ♪
♪ In cars ♪
♪ In trucks ♪
(Tom laughing)
- [Crow] I got a kooky
idea for a new song.
- And now what are we gonna do?
- Find the rangers and tell
them what's happened to you.
- It's a bit late.
- It's more important
now than ever before.
You saw them, those
marks on her face.
- It's horrible.
- [Tom] Oh, just go
out and get yourself
a new pair of disco
camping boots there, dear.
- Bill, warm up the Jeep.
- Molly, the road is in
a terrible condition.
- Come on, Bill.
If anyone can get
through, you can.
We've got to try.
- Listen, I'll come with
you, I'll just get--
- No, I'll go.
You stay with Sharon.
- Why don't we all
go in the camper?
- [Joel] Oh, just go!
Somebody.
- What about the phone, then?
- The lines are still down.
I just tried it.
- Well, that's it.
- What are we gonna do?
- Find the rangers?
- [Crow] Pepperidge
Farm remembers.
(thunder rumbling)
- [Tom] Mm, mm, mm, mm.
You're a good kid.
- [Joel] Remind me
to use you later.
- [Crow] Hope she doesn't miss
her Josie and the
Pussycats audition.
- [Joel] You know,
I never liked him.
- [Tom] Aloha.
Auf wiedersehen.
(thunder rumbling)
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
Okay, you've drawn Siegfried.
Now, where's Roy?
- That's my mommy.
- [Crow] Ah!
- [Tom] Ooh.
- Do you have a mommy?
- [Crow] He was
born of an omelet.
Of course not.
- You don't know?
Does she look like this?
- [Crow] Ooh.
- [Tom] No, no.
- Or like this?
- [Tom] Any distinguishing
marks or scars?
- Where is she, then?
- [Crow] Where did
he learn English?
- Oh, she's in a tree.
- [Joel] I can tell by the
expression on your face
that you loved her so, Trumpy.
- [Tom] What, she's
from Rand McNally?
- On a star?
- [Crow] Can she carry
moonbeams home in a jar?
- Wow!
With this you can see the stars.
You want to look?
- [Tom] This kid
sounds like Georgette.
- [Joel] Yeah.
- [Crow] Kitty!
- [Joel] Oh, they got "Wild
Kingdom" on the telescope.
- [Tom] Cool.
(drums beating)
- [Joel] Mm-hmm.
And drums, too?
- You can do magic things.
- [Crow] It's called evil, kid.
- [Tom] He's got
his high beams on.
Hmm?
- [Joel] He's got
Bette Davis eyes.
(Tom laughs)
- [Crow] Orphan Annie eyes.
- [Joel] Oh, great,
now we're in "Gumby."
- [Crow] I'm gonna go
walk through a book.
-
[Tom]
Ooh,
it's
supercalafragilistic-expialidocious.
(Tom giggles)
D'oh.
- [Crow] I love this,
it's so spontaneous.
- [Tom] Woo!
- [Joel] Oh, wow, we're in
"Pee-Wee's Playhouse" now.
- [Crow] Oh, yuck.
It's a Peter Gabriel video.
- [Tom] Yeah, somebody
hit that kid in the head
with a sledgehammer. (laughing)
- [Joel] Wow.
Oh, this alien makes
student films, huh?
- [Tom] What, did he come
from Planet Goofball?
Did he come here in
a little clown car?
Criminy.
- [Joel] Great,
now he can remake
"Rudolph's Shiny New Year."
(Tom chuckling)
- [Tom] Poor rabbit.
- [Crow] Poor us.
- Trumpy?
Where are you?
- [Crow] Get me!
I'm Lionel Richie!
- [Joel] That's not right.
- Trumpy.
- [Tom] Huh?
- Hey, come back down.
- [Tom] Really looked
like a ceiling, didn't it?
Oh, fun.
- [Crow] Whew!
- Tommy, what are you doing?
- [Joel] It's just my
Spike Jones album, Mom!
- [Tom] Tommy, now,
you quit warping
time and space this instant.
- Tommy.
Did you hear me, Tommy?
- Come on, quickly.
Hide in there.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, Mom.
- What's going on here?
- Little Joe got out.
- What?
- My hamster Joe escaped.
- Well, try and be a
little more careful.
I told you a thousand
times, I don't want you--
- [Tom] I'd like some
breakfast, please.
- Turning this house into a zoo.
And stop fidgeting
around like that.
- Yes, Mommy.
- All right, now come
downstairs with me
and behave yourself.
I've got enough problems.
- [Tom] Make that
three hard-boiled eggs.
- [Crow] I've got
to get a series.
- [Joel] Now, do you think
those are blue contacts,
or are his eyes
naturally that color?
- [Tom] Oh, you mean,
like Whoopi Goldberg?
(Tom laughs)
Get my head caught
in the snout there.
- [Crow] Now to find a herd
of cattle to drain dry.
- [Tom] Meanwhile, in a
winter movie somewhere.
- [Joel] Gosh, that
last scene was goofy.
I'm glad we weren't in it.
- Ah, sometimes there is.
- I thought hunting wasn't
allowed around here.
- It's not.
- Why are you carrying
this rifle, then?
- [Tom] For you.
- Well, if that friend of
yours Laura had carried one,
she'd still be alive.
- [Joel] Hurts.
- [Tom] Ooh.
- [Crow] Hey, it's a
matching shirt and sofa set.
- [Tom] Hi, gang.
(Tom humming)
Hmm, not bad.
Oh, the new Vogue is here.
- Molly, is the
television working?
- I think so, yes.
- Well, at least we won't
miss "Dallas" this week.
- [Crow] Oh great,
your friend just died
and you're gonna watch "Dallas?"
- [Tom] Shh.
- Tracy, how can you
kid around like this,
things being the way they are?
- [Tom] Thank you.
- Because if I didn't,
I'd be in hysterics.
It doesn't work.
- [Joel] I'm in hysterics!
- That's strange.
It was working yesterday.
- [Joel] I rerouted
the power into Trumpy.
- The radio makes
a funny noise, too.
- [Tom] That's called music.
- Can I go back
to my room, Mommy?
- Yes, you can.
- [Crow] For the
rest of your life.
- [Kathy] How is Sharon?
- She's gone to bed.
She was shattered.
- [Joel] This town's in tatters.
- [Tom] Shadoobie.
- So peaceful, so quiet.
(Tracy chuckles)
(Tom chuckles)
- Trumpy.
(Joel hissing)
(Tom chuckles)
- [Tom] Face it, kid.
Trumpy never loved you.
Boo!
Gotcha! (laughs)
- [Tommy] Trumpy, where are you?
- [Joel] Were ties
ever that wide?
- Ah.
- [Tom] Ah.
- [Crow] All right.
S'all right.
- [Joel] Nothin'.
- [Crow] Hmm.
(cat meows)
- Have you seen Trumpy?
- [Joel] He tried to eat me.
He's evil.
- [Tom] Forget you.
Boo! (laughs)
(upbeat music)
Cujo?
- [Joel] Evil one?
- [Joel] Supreme being?
- [Crow] Alf?
- [Tom] Chief?
- [Crow] McCloud?
- Trumpy, come on.
Where are you?
- [Crow] He seeks him here.
He seeks him there.
He seeks that rascal everywhere.
- [Tom] Ah, don't
worry about him.
He's moody and introspective.
He's in a corner reading
"Swimming to Cambodia".
- [Crow] Hmm.
- Trumpy, are you in here?
- [Joel] This is, like, the
house of a million foyers.
(suspenseful music)
- [Crow] Dad?
- [Tom] Dum.
- [Tom] Don't go
into the dining room.
- [Joel] Here's Tommy!
- Trumpy.
- [Joel] Sounds like music from
the "High Plains
Drifter," doesn't it?
- [Crow] Yeah.
- [Tom] Has a Sergio
Leone feel to it.
- [Crow] Bad choice.
- [Joel] Oh, those are
ready to pop, I would say.
- [Tom] Oh, thank goodness
it's summer again.
We've been driving for months.
- Doesn't look
like anybody's in.
- But how can you
tell from here?
- [Tom] Oh, why don't you
just go up to the door?
You drove two
seasons to get here.
For crying out loud.
- [Crow] Boy, he's
really burning oil.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
- [Joel] I'm gonna let
this do the talking.
- Charley?
Jack?
Is anyone there?
- [Joel] He knows 'em,
and he's bringing a gun?
- [Tom] Oh, it's a
little practical joke.
He kicks open the door and
plugs them with 30 rounds.
It's kind of an inside
family thing, you know.
- [Crow] Housewarming gift.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
- [Joel] Ah!
- [Tom] Ooh.
- [Joel] Oh, it's that guy.
- What do you think you're--
- Shh.
- [Joel] Hey, Bill, are those
Haggar slacks you're wearing?
Farah?
Dad N' Lad?
The Guys?
(Tom chuckling)
- [Crow] Watch this.
Little joke.
Hi, we're the cast
from "Straw Dogs."
(Crow laughing)
- [Tom] Sometimes it works.
Watchtower!
Oh, just kidding.
(Tom and Crow chuckle)
That thing in the magazine.
- What the hell happened here?
- [Tom] Hmm.
- [Joel] Hmm.
- The radio's not working.
- [Crow] Oh, nuts, I wanted
to hear Shadoe Stevens.
- Charley?
Jack?
- [Joel] Biff?
Happy?
Anybody?
- You think they're
in the other room?
- After all this
shouting, I sure hope not.
- [Joel] Horse poster
compliments Dynamite magazine.
For teens.
- [Crow] Turkey legs
in the... (groans)
- He's dead, I think.
- [Tom] His last
words were, "Huzzah!"
- What's that?
Same mark that Laura had.
Is he one of the rangers?
- [Joel] No, but we could
dress him like a ranger.
- No, he's a poacher,
name of Matt Collins.
Let's get the hell out of here.
I don't know.
- Look out!
Jesus!
- [Crow] Ah!
Alf's back, and this
time it's personal.
(Tom chuckling)
- [Tom] Ooh, Reagan's next.
- [Crow] Pepperidge
Farm remembers!
Pepperidge Farm remembers!
The heck with it.
I'm getting out of here!
Crackers or no.
- [Tom] That is the frumpiest
monster I've ever seen.
- [Joel] Yep.
- [Crow] Hey, wait,
you got coupons comin'.
- [Joel] No hitchhikers,
it's company policy.
- [Tom] Ooh.
Ah, enough of that
exciting stuff.
Meanwhile, in still
yet another movie.
(Crow sighs)
(Tom hiccups)
- [Crow] What the?
- You're a good cook, Tracy.
Unusual with girls today.
- Well, my mother taught me.
She always said
that men like you
for your meat, and
after your dessert.
You know how it is.
If you haven't got a
pretty face to begin with,
there's nothing you can do.
- [Joel] Well, I think your
mother had a filthy mouth.
- Including the
seven-day beauty plan.
- [Tom] Didn't work.
- Come on, it's not that bad.
You've got a lot of good points.
- Yeah, and I know
the ones men like.
These and this.
- But you're very intelligent.
- Yeah, I don't know what
threatens the guys more,
my face or my intelligence.
- [Crow] Yeah, E
equals MC-squared.
- Hey, I'm getting a bit
worried about Brian and Bill.
They've been gone now for hours.
- Oh, maybe they got held up.
Or couldn't find the rangers.
- Oh, yeah, these rangers.
- [Joel] Down, girl.
Heel.
Take it easy.
- All right, Molly, I know.
Just in case, however,
I'm going to get
my makeup from the camper.
I forgot it last night.
- [Tom] Take a cold shower.
- Now, what's going on, Tommy?
You've been running
in and out all day.
What are you looking for?
- Nothing.
Just getting some water for Joe.
- Oh.
- Joe?
Are you hiding a man
somewhere in this house?
- Joe is Tommy's hamster, Tracy.
- Oh, what a shame.
- [Tom] Jeez, Tracy, stay
away from the kid's animals.
(thunder rumbling)
(Tom humming)
(Crow whistles)
- [Crow] Ba-dump-a-dee,
time to Armor All my pants.
- [Joel] Oh, this is great.
He's gonna do that
Bob Newhart routine.
(Tom chuckles)
- [Tom] Love that.
- [Joel] Abner?
Yeah, hello.
- Still isn't working.
Where the hell have Brian
and that old geezer got to?
It's been seven hours
since they left.
Didn't have that far to go.
Maybe something
happened to them.
- Wouldn't surprise me.
Bill's as thick as two planks.
- [Crow] Is he green-treated?
- How are Sharon and Kathy?
- They took sleeping
pills and went to bed.
They were absolutely
scared out of their wits.
Maybe you should do the same.
- [Tom] Maybe you
should do the same.
(thunder rumbling)
- [Joel] Trumpy?
I brought you a cup of treacle.
- Trumpy.
Where are you hiding?
- [Crow] Hey, she's
got her L.L. Bean
disco survival boots on.
- [Tom] Survive in style.
- [Joel] Trumpy,
bring me the girl.
I desire to be read to.
(tense music)
- [Tom] Neil Peart on drums.
- [Crow] Hey, it's Craig
Wasson, all of a sudden.
- [Joel] Now Trumpy and
I will do my version
of "Rear Window."
(woman screams)
- [Tom] I think
she found Trumpy.
- [All] Wah, wah, wah.
- [Crow] Hey, this is not
healthy for a little boy.
I can't watch.
- [Joel] Trumpy, no.
I told you no.
- Trumpy.
- [Tom] When good pets do bad
things, on "A Current Affair."
- [Joel] That was neat.
(boy gasps)
Trumpy, we hardly knew ye.
(Tom coughs)
- [Tom] Put out the van.
Oh, so people are being
methodically killed
by the Banana Splits.
(gunshot bangs)
- [Joel] There goes Drooper.
Fleegle.
- [Tom] Snork.
(gunshot bangs)
- Oh, my God.
- Bill.
- [Bill] So what, she's dead?
- Yeah, she is.
What the hell's going on?
- It was a damned animal.
- What animal?
- [Crow] The damned one.
- Where's Brian?
- He's dead.
- Dead, where?
- Back at the hut.
- [Crow] Oh, take the
Baretta hat off, old man.
- [Tom] Aww.
(Tom chuckles)
Faster, Trumpy, kill, kill.
- What the hell?
What's happening?
Answer me, you goat.
What is this?
What have you done,
you old bastard?
- Stop it!
Have you both gone crazy?
- I want to know who
it was killed Brian,
and Tracy, and why.
- I told you.
- [Tom] We have to go.
- It was that weird animal.
And if we stay here,
it'll kill us all.
- What sort of
fairy tale is this?
- Oh, listen, Rick.
We'll sort this out later.
Now help Bill
carry Tracy inside.
Bill.
- You are magic,
aren't you, Trumpy?
(circus music)
Trumpy, you come down.
(Tom shouting)
(circus music)
I can't bring 'em down.
I don't know how it works.
(circus music)
I'm stuck!
Oh, we got commercial sign!
- I really don't know what
kind of animal it was.
All I know is I was very lucky.
- Whatever it is, it's
already killed four people,
and maybe more.
Where are you going, Rick?
- To wake up the girls.
- Why?
- So we can get outta here.
I ain't hanging about to find
out who's next for the chop.
- You can't leave now.
- No, why not?
- [Tom] I made quiche.
- It's getting dark,
'cause the road's blocked,
because that thing,
that murderous animal
is maybe waiting for us.
- [Crow] Yeah, but
give me a good reason.
- He's right, you know.
We better wait till morning.
- Listen, I'm sick and tired
of hearing the same old story.
- [Joel] I'm sick and tired
of being sick and tired.
- How can you say that, Rick?
- Well, I'm getting out of here,
and if I were you, I'd
take the kid and leave.
- [Tom] Kid?
What kid?
Oh my god!
- [Crow] Don't start
with me, Martha.
- If you've got a bit of
sense, then, you'll stay.
- He's right, Rick.
He knows the forest.
- I'd better make sure
that all the doors
and windows are bolted.
- [Joel] Now for
some peach cobbler.
- [Tom] Oh, George,
get me a drink.
Boo?
Boo Radley?
- [Crow] Dark One?
Beelzebub?
- [Joel] Chief?
- [Crow] McCloud?
Trumpage, Trumpazoid,
the Trumpmonster.
- [Tom] Trumparino!
- [Crow] Stretching the premise.
- [Tom] Yeah.
- [Joel] He knocked his block
off, but you can press it
back down again with the Rock
'Em Sock 'Em Robots by Marx.
- [Tom] So, what can I get ya?
Ouzo, vodka, Sambuca,
Pernod, Frangelico,
Blue Curacao, Glenmorangie,
B&B, Hennessy,
Tanqueray, 100-year-old brandy?
- I've never needed a
gun to defend myself.
- Yeah, right.
You probably pay
others to defend you.
- [Tom] No, I use a
woman as a shield.
(gun clicks)
- What the hell are you doing?
- [Crow] Beer and a
shot, like you said.
- [Tom] All right,
all right, I'll get
the smoky 12-year-old scotch.
(gunshot bangs)
- What are you doing?
- [Joel] He shot my Jim
Beam pheasant decanter!
- He's gone crazy.
- Look, what is it with you two?
Haven't we got enough trouble?
- I don't like
anyone bugging me.
(knocking on door)
- [Tommy] Mommy, open
the door, let me in.
- It's Tommy.
- [Tom] I'll get him.
(imitates gun clicking)
- [Crow] Tommy, throw open
the door and say "pull."
- Where did you spring from?
- [Joel] From your loins, Mommy.
- Didn't I tell you
to stay in your room?
- I went to pick some
plants for all the--
- Plants for all your
animals, I suppose, right?
That's it.
Out they're going to
go in the morning.
Now get to your room and
don't move till I tell you to.
- Wake up, Kathy.
- [Tom] I think I got
something to say to you.
- I heard a shot.
- Shot?
You must've been dreaming.
- Wake up!
- What time is it?
- [Tom] You know, I'm starting
not to believe this movie.
I believed it when Alf
went on the killing spree,
but now I don't know.
- I don't know, I just hear
voices from downstairs.
- Wow, those pills
sure are strong.
I'm gonna take a shower
and try to wake myself up.
- That's a good idea,
but don't take too long.
- [Tom] Oh.
- [Crow] Honey, I'm home,
oh, I'm a little kid.
- [Joel] Nosy?
- [Tom] Chirpy?
- [Crow] Ratboy?
Sondra Locke?
- [Tom] Chief?
- [Crow] McCloud?
- [Joel] Now, for my wonderful
experiment of joining
a duck's body to
a rabbit's head.
There.
(Tom humming)
- [Tom] Hey, the
evil one's back.
- Trumpy.
- [Crow] Hey, it's like
that scene in "Mac and Me"
when Mac came back to life.
- No, stay there.
Why did you kill that girl?
Why did you do that?
Now I can't be your
friend anymore.
- [Tom] Bad hell beast.
- [Crow] Did it for the kicks.
- You're naughty, Trumpy.
Very naughty.
- [Joel] Where have
you been, young man?
This is not a hotel.
- You wouldn't
kill me, would you?
Trumpy, was it you?
- [Tom] I like you, Tommy.
I'll kill you last.
- Are you saying
there's another one?
Listen, Trumpy, Uncle
Bill wants to kill you.
- [Joel] My advice,
don't let him.
Looks real bad for you, man.
- What can we do?
- [Tom] Oh, you could put
on a play in the backyard.
Trumpy could play Cyrano.
- You can't stay here anymore.
And I don't want you to go.
Listen, we'll go together
and hide in the woods.
No, wait here.
I'll find you a disguise.
- [Crow] What do you think
he's gonna dress him up as,
Drew Barrymore?
- [Joel] Henry Thomas he's not.
- [Crow] No.
- [Tom] Oh, suddenly I
feel like someone should be
reading a Robert Frost poem.
Something there is that doesn't
love a crummy monster film.
That's from "Mending Monster
Film" by Robert Frost.
- [Crow] Neat.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
- [Crow] Mint julep? (belches)
- [Tom] No thanks, I've had 12.
- [Joel] Sure hope
the liquor holds out.
- [Tom] I don't know.
(Joel humming)
♪ I'm in the shower,
nothing will happen to me ♪
- [Crow] Norman?
Norman?
Important phone call.
- [Tom] I wonder
if Bobby likes me.
I like him.
- [Joel] Check it out,
product placement right there.
Yep.
(Tom chuckling)
- [Tom] "Die Hard
2" this is not.
- [Crow] Hmm.
Coke, Sprite, Pepto-Bismol,
United Airlines,
Steve Guttenberg.
- [Tom] Uh-huh.
There, now you look
like Admiral Peary
playing the Elephant Man.
- Hold on a minute.
I'll go and investigate.
- [Joel] Trumpy felt scarred
by his ugly hillbilly nose.
- [Crow] Looks like a
baseball bat from Alaska.
- [Tom] Oh, Velvet Hammer?
Harvey Wallbanger?
Pink Squirrel?
Little hair of the
alien that bit ya?
(Tom chuckles)
(Crow humming)
- [Crow] I'm naked and
all alone in the shower.
I'm totally vulnerable and
somebody could kill me.
(Crow humming)
- [Tom] It's probably likely
at this point in the film.
- [Crow] My brain fell out.
- [Joel] Say, I
look just like fog.
- [Tom] Hmm?
- [Joel] Oh.
(Crow imitating squeaking)
- [Crow] You need
a protein rinse.
And you have dandruff.
- [Tom] Honey...
(Kathy screams)
- [Crow] What?
What, what?
What?
(Kathy screaming)
- [Tom] Wait, wait, I
made you a special drink.
Don't forget the coaster!
- Rick!
Brian!
- [Tom] Somebody!
- [Rick] Kathy!
(Kathy screams)
- [Tom] Ooh.
- [Crow] Don't look
at me without makeup.
- [Tom] Whoa.
- [Joel] Oops.
- [Rick] Open the door!
- [Crow] But not
with your skull.
- [Sharon] Molly!
- What's happened?
- It's Kathy.
- [Tom] She's zestfully
dead. (chuckling)
(gunshot bangs)
- [Tom] Ow.
- Quickly, get her onto the bed.
- [Joel] You know,
this might sound crass,
but we're getting
really good at this.
- [Crow] They're gonna
have to build an addition
just to stack the bodies.
- What's happening here?
- [Tom] How big is
a cord of bodies?
- What was that thing?
- [Crow] Depends on
how you stack them.
- [Bill] Some kind
of weird animal.
- Where are Brian and Tracy?
- [Joel] What have I done?
Oh my goodness.
- Trumpy, what are
you doing here?
- Go on.
[Tom] Killing people.
- Tommy?
- [Joel] Can you hear me?
- Tommy!
- [Joel] Can you
feel me near you?
- We can't play now.
Something's happened downstairs.
You've gotta hide.
- [Crow] You're my alibi, kid.
- [Tom] They'll kill you.
They'll kill you dead.
- [Joel] This
thing smells musty.
- Tommy.
- [Tommy] What is it, Mom?
- Are you all right, son?
- Mm-hmm.
- [Crow] Well,
relatively speaking, yes.
Depends on what the norm is.
- Are you sure we ought
to go after it now, Bill?
- Now's the time to
finish the damn thing off,
once and for all.
It's wounded, and we
can follow its trail.
- Don't go, Rick.
- Isn't it better to
wait till morning?
- I tell you, Molly.
Now is the time
to finish it off.
- But, Bill, why don't you
leave it for the rangers?
Isn't it their--
- Molly, we can't just sit here
waiting for it to come
back and kill us all.
- [Tom] Yeah, we
got plenty of booze.
Let's go ahead.
- And we gotta do it now.
- It's not a monster.
It wants to be our friend.
- How can you say that
after all that's happened?
- 'Cause it's true.
They all wanna be our friends,
but we won't let them.
- That's enough talking--
- [Joel] Oh, that's silly.
Finish your tequila.
- We'll be careful.
- Don't go.
There's been enough killing.
- [Crow] Stop the madness!
- [Tom] Last call, everybody.
Finish 'em up.
- You coming or not?
- [Tom] We'll take a bottle.
Got a hip flask in the car.
- [Joel] Hey, he's
mixing his leathers now.
- [Crow] Wonder
what they wanted?
Hmm.
(Tom humming)
- Sharon!
- Huh?
- Tommy, both of you,
quickly, come over here!
Get away from it!
(Tom chuckling)
- Ooh my god!
- [Tommy] No, Mommy,
don't shoot him.
- Tommy!
- Trumpy is good.
It wasn't him.
- [Joel] What he's done is good.
- Tommy, get away from it!
- No, Mommy, don't shoot.
Please.
- [Tom] Don't make
your mother kill him.
- Tommy, it's going to kill you!
- [Crow] I know what
you're thinking, Tommy.
Did mom fire six
shots or only five?
- [Molly] Tommy!
(tense music)
- [Joel] John Bonham, Moby Dick.
- Tommy!
Tommy, come back!
(upbeat music)
(tense music)
- [Joel] John Bonham, Moby Dick.
- Tommy!
Tommy, come back!
- [Tom] Come back, Shane!
- Come back!
Tommy!
- [Crow] Run, Rusty, run.
- [Tom] Run, Eliza, run.
- [Joel] You know, that
Trumpy is one ugly--
- [Crow And Tom] Shut yo' mouth.
- [Joel] Hey, I'm only talking
about Trumpy, can you dig it?
- [Bill] We have to cross
over to the other side.
Let's go.
- [Tom] Break on through
to the other side, man.
(Tom laughs)
- [Crow] Buddy Rich on drums.
- [Tom] Backed up
by Bill Kreutzmann.
- [Molly] Tommy!
Tommy!
Where are you?
- [Tom] Fortunately,
Molly was a LLRP in 'Nam
and knows how to track a
boy with a snout-nosed pal.
- [Bill] I walked down
stream in the water.
It's clever.
- We'll never find him now.
- Tommy!
- [Kathy] We must go faster.
- [Crow] Yeah, yeah,
keep your shirt on.
I'm wearing a big stuffed suit.
- [Rick] Not a trace.
- [Tom] Who?
- [Rick] We'll have
to wait till daylight.
- [Crow] Daylight looks
like night anyhow.
What's it now?
- [Tom] Day for night, I think.
- [Crow] Oh.
Thank you, Truffaut.
- [Joel] Well, let's go home.
Our job is done here.
- [Tommy] Someone's coming.
Get down.
- [Crow] Splendor in the grass.
- [Tom] Grazing in
the grass is a gas.
- [Joel] Can you dig it?
- [Crow] High-weed surfin'.
- [Tommy] Shh.
- [Tom] Shh!
Would you--
- [Tommy] They mustn't find us.
(Tom coughs)
- [Tom] Vapor action.
- Trumpy.
Trumpy, where are you hiding?
(whistling theme from "Lassie")
(Tom coughing)
- [Tom] Boy, he's gonna
need that gas mask.
- [Crow] Oh, Trumpy, gross.
- [Tom] You stepped
in some Trumpy-dumpy.
- [Joel] You guys, come on.
(Tommy gasps)
- [Joel] Whoops. (chuckles)
- [Tom] I'm gonna
batter fry you, kid.
- [Crow] Come on,
over the plate, man.
- Mommy!
- [Crow] Come on,
rocket it in, man.
Over the plate, come on.
- Trumpy!
- [Tom] Kid, you were set up.
- Mommy!
- Sounded like Tommy.
- [Crow] No, it wasn't.
It was "Mommy."
It was an M sound.
Mmm, like Manhattan, mimosa.
- Tommy!
- Tommy, where are you?
- [Joel] This is,
like, more intense
than when Bobby Brady got
lost in the Grand Canyon.
- [Tom] Oh, no,
wasn't that in Hawaii?
- [Joel] No, that was where
Peter found that Buddha thing.
- [Crow] Oh, yeah.
That was cool.
- Oh, yeah.
- [Tommy] Don't hurt me.
I'm not like the others.
(Tom and Joel mewing)
- [Crow] Ouch.
(Tom mewing)
- [Tommy] I just wanna
help you, that's all.
- [Crow] Stay away from
that, it still hurts.
- I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
I'd just like to help you.
- [Joel] I conspire
against my own.
(Tom mewing)
- I'll blast one,
you take the other.
- No, please don't hurt them.
- Get out of the way, Tommy!
Get out of the way!
- No, don't hurt them, please.
- [Tom] Move it, kid.
I'll have a banana
daiquiri, please.
(gunshots banging)
- No, Bill!
(Bill shouting)
- [Tom] Long Island iced tea.
(gunshot bangs)
(creature screams)
- [Joel] Hey, looks like he
came from the Dumbo planet.
- [Crow] Time to take the
mask off and see who it is.
Do you folks at home know?
- [Molly] Tommy!
- [Crow] Oh, my ankle,
it's all bendy-wendy.
- [Sharon] Molly,
we'll find him.
- [Tom] We may find him
dead, but we will find him.
- [Joel] Boy, I hope he left
the keys to the liquor cabinet.
- [Tom] Poor sap.
- [Crow] Oh,
self-burying monster.
Explain that.
- [Tom] Soft beach.
- [Sharon] Oh. (gasping)
- [Joel] And he died as he
lived, with his mouth wide open.
- [Molly] Where's Tommy?
- He went that way.
Wait, Molly!
Come on.
- Trumpy, I'm sorry.
- [Molly] Tommy!
Tommy, answer me, please!
- [Crow] State it in
the form of a question.
- [Molly] Tommy!
- [Tom] Come to the mirror, boy!
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
- [Tommy] It's just no good.
No, Trumpy, they'll never
let us stay together.
You frighten them,
you understand?
- [Tom] For obvious reasons.
- [Tommy] I'll never
forget you, Trumpy.
- [Tom] The way you callously
knocked off 15 people.
I'll never forget that.
Don't ever change, Trumpy.
Aww.
- [Joel] A tender moment.
- [Tommy] Now please
go and don't come back.
Do you understand?
Don't ever come back.
- [Molly] Tommy, where are you?
- Go away, Trumpy.
I hate you.
Go away.
- [Joel] Oh, boy, that kid's
really having mood swings.
- We're not friends anymore.
- [Joel] That's not good.
- Go away.
All right, Trumpy.
(Tom mewing)
I'll go, then.
I'm over here, Mommy!
- [Crow] Talkin' to Billy Barty.
(Tom mewing)
- [Tommy] Mommy, I'm here!
- [Rick] Molly, he's here.
- [Joel] No, he's over there.
- [Molly] Tommy!
- Mom!
- [Tom] Sorry, boy,
your uncle's dead,
but if there's a God
and he tends bar,
your uncle's bellying
up right about now.
- Yes, Tommy, all the
monsters are dead.
Isn't that right?
(synth music)
♪ It's been seven ♪
- [Tom] Oh, nevermind.
- [Crow] Hey, don't
leave me here.
I was raised by a child.
I can't survive
in the wilderness.
(Tom mewing)
I'll just wait here, then.
- [Tom] So. (sighs)
- [Crow] Hmm.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
♪ I've laughed with monsters ♪
♪ I've cried with monsters ♪
♪ I'll die with
monsters from hell ♪
- [Crow] I'm
getting out of here.
This place sucks.
(Tom chuckles)
Going back to my planet.
- [Tom] Hmm, Marine?
Send in the marines.
- [Crow] Hey.
- [Joel] Ah, isn't that
Martin Sheen's son?
- [Crow] Hey, who isn't?
- [Joel] Yeah,
got a point there.
- [Tom] Yep.
Ooh, that's a good
Italian lunch wine.
Very light.
Smooth palate, a
nice woody finish.
- [Joel] Hey, Martin and
Lewis were in this movie.
- [Crow] Come on, Jerry,
we've got the rest
of the credits to get through.
- [Joel] Wow, Dean.
- [Crow] Aw, quit
horsing around, boy.
(Tom sniffs)
- [Tom] Ah, the fresh
smell of Emanuel Pine.
- [Crow] Long needle.
- [Joel] I say
both of those guys
were in the Knights of Columbus.
- [Tom] I think they're Two
Guys of the Rotten Union
is what it is.
- [Crow] Well, hmm.
- [Tom] Oh, I thought
I smelled basil.
Basil!
- [Crow] Yes, dear.
I'm doing it, dear.
How can I do it if
you keep calling me?
You great cow!
- [Joel] Come on,
let's get out of here.
- [Crow] Oh, thank you.
- [Tom] Chase me.
- [Crow] Okay. (laughs)
- Well, guys, looks like it's
time to pack it all in again.
- Yeah, we are the stuff
dreams are made of.
- Oh, that's beautiful, Crow.
Shakespeare?
- No, Burma-Shave.
- Oh, well, huh?
- You know, guys, it always
hurts to close it all up.
- Yeah.
- Strike the set.
- Ow!
- Wipe off the grease paint.
Napkin up the blood and entrails
and move on to another town.
- Uh-oh, I smell a song.
- Mm-hmm.
♪ Tell me, where does
all the magic go ♪
♪ When the curtain
falls to end the show ♪
♪ Do the clowns always cry ♪
♪ When they pack
up the paper sky ♪
♪ When the champagne
is being poured ♪
♪ And the lock is on
the old stage door ♪
♪ Will there still be
a clown in the sky ♪
♪ For me ♪
(Tom sobbing)
- No.
- Don't worry, buddy.
There'll be other experiments.
- You really think so, mister?
- Yeah, take a verse,
it'll cheer you up.
- Okay.
♪ When the harlequin
is on the bed ♪
♪ And the whisky haze
surrounds his head ♪
♪ William Holden's coming over ♪
- Tom Servo.
♪ And he's got a fifth of ♪
If you don't stop doing
your Anthony Newley,
I'm gonna throw you
against the wall.
- He'll do it, too.
♪ Will there still be
a clown in the sky ♪
- Help us out, Crow.
♪ Still be a clown in the sky ♪
Take it home, Joel.
♪ Tell me, where is
that clown in the sky ♪
♪ For me ♪
(Tom sobbing)
- I love you, Tom Servo.
- I love you, Joel.
- I love you, Crow.
- You're not my real father.
- What do you think, sirs?
- It stinks.
(solemn music)
- Well?
- It stinks.